class Questions {
  static final brainTeasersForKids = [
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0People make me, save me, change me, raise me. What am I?",
      "Answer": "Money",
      "A": "Money",
      "B": "Children",
      "C": "Property",
      "D": "Water"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "What has a face and two or three hands but no arms or legs?\u00a0",
      "Answer": "A clock",
      "A": "Bag",
      "B": "A Clock",
      "C": "Fowl",
      "D": "All of the above"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Why are ghosts bad at lying?",
      "Answer": "Because you can see right through them.",
      "A": "Because they are ghost",
      "B": "They don't lie",
      "C": "I don't know",
      "D": "Because you can see right through them"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "What five-letter word gets shorter when you add two letters to it?\u00a0",
      "Answer": "Short",
      "A": "Shorter",
      "B": "No letter like that",
      "C": "Short",
      "D": "All letters"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "With pointed fangs I sit and wait; with piercing force I crunch out fate; grabbing victims, proclaiming might; physically joining with a single bite. What am I?",
      "Answer": "A stapler",
      "A": "A stapler",
      "B": "Niddle",
      "C": "Hungry Lion",
      "D": "Nail and hammer"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0A word I know, six letters it contains, remove one letter and 12 remains, what is it?",
      "Answer": "Dozens",
      "A": "Million",
      "B": "Sieze",
      "C": "Dozens",
      "D": "All of the above"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0I am always hungry and will die if not fed, but if you water me, I\u2019ll die. What am I?\u00a0",
      "Answer": "A fire",
      "A": "Sand",
      "B": "A fire",
      "C": "Cloth",
      "D": "An Insect"
    },
    {
      "Question": "\u00a0How many letters are there in the English alphabet?",
      "Answer":
          "18. 3 in \u2018the\u2019, 7 in \u2018English,\u2019 and 8 in \u2018alphabet.\u2019",
      "A": "1 to infinity",
      "B": "26",
      "C":
          "18. 3 in \u2018the\u2019, 7 in \u2018English,\u2019 and 8 in \u2018alphabet.\u2019",
      "D": "None of the above"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0What breaks yet never falls, and what falls yet never breaks?",
      "Answer": "Morning and night",
      "A": "Paper",
      "B": "Ball",
      "C": "Morning and night",
      "D": "None of them"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Turn us on our backs and open up our stomachs, and you will be the wisest but at the start a lummox. What are we?",
      "Answer": "Books",
      "A": "Laptops",
      "B": "Specimens",
      "C": "None of them",
      "D": "Books"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What type of cheese is made backward?\u00a0",
      "Answer": "Edam",
      "A": "Fries",
      "B": "Cheese",
      "C": "Edam",
      "D": "All of the above"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0What is always in front of you but can\u2019t be seen?",
      "Answer": "The future",
      "A": "The Future",
      "B": "Fore Head",
      "C": "Next question",
      "D": "Don't know"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0The more you take, the more you leave behind. What are they?",
      "Answer": "Footsteps",
      "A": "Water",
      "B": "Footsteps",
      "C": "Cloth",
      "D": "Sand"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What\u2019s black, white, and blue?\u00a0",
      "Answer": "A sad zebra",
      "A": "A sad zebra",
      "B": "Camellion",
      "C": "Estonia flag",
      "D": "Pigeon"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0\u00a0I turn once, what is out will not get in. I turn again, what is in will not get out. What am I?",
      "Answer": "A key",
      "A": "Pit",
      "B": "A key",
      "C": "Addiction",
      "D": "Nail"
    },
    {
      "Question": "\u00a0What is the end of everything?",
      "Answer": "The letter \u201cg\u201d",
      "A": "Cloud",
      "B": "The letter \u201cg\u201d",
      "C": "Death",
      "D": "Water"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0I am a word of letters three; add two and fewer there will be. What word am I?",
      "Answer": "Few",
      "A": "Three",
      "B": "Few",
      "C": "I Don't know",
      "D": "A and B"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What has to be broken before you can use it?\u00a0",
      "Answer": "An egg",
      "A": "A Promise",
      "B": "Ice Block",
      "C": "An egg",
      "D": "Block"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Which jungle animal is hiding \u201cinside\u201d these letters \u2013 L P H N?",
      "Answer": "An elephant",
      "A": "Python",
      "B": "An elephant",
      "C": "Lion",
      "D": "Nigro"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0A mouse wants to get in better shape. She\u2019s going to start by climbing the stairs. Starting on the fourth floor, she climbs up five stories, down seven stories, up six stories, down three stories, and up four stories again. What floor is she on?",
      "Answer": "The ninth floor",
      "A": "There's no stairs",
      "B": "The mouse is already is good shape",
      "C": "The ninth floor",
      "D": "The 14th floor"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Can you add one mathematical symbol in between 55555 to equal 500?",
      "Answer": "555-55=500",
      "A": "It's not possible",
      "B": "555-55=500",
      "C": "555/32",
      "D": "55500"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0What letters are easily found in every single day of the week?",
      "Answer": "D-A-Y",
      "A": "D-A-Y",
      "B": "E-A",
      "C": "Friday",
      "D": "Week days"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0What\u2019s left when you take an ant out of a plantain?",
      "Answer": "Something plain",
      "A": "Hole",
      "B": "Something plain",
      "C": "The plantain",
      "D": "More ants"
    },
    "Related: 101\u00a0Fun Facts",
    {
      "Question":
          " Jason turned left, right, spun around 360\u00b0, stood on his head, and then walked backward before taking a picture of the sunset. What direction was he pointing?",
      "Answer": "West",
      "A": "South",
      "B": "East",
      "C": "North",
      "D": "West"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Paul the Polar Bear had a birthday party, with each guest bringing five fish. A nasty little penguin stole two fish but there were still 198 fish left. How many people came to the party?",
      "Answer": "40",
      "A": "39",
      "B": "28",
      "C": "40",
      "D": "90"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0If tomorrow I said \u201cthe day before yesterday was Saturday\u201d, which day is today?",
      "Answer": "Sunday",
      "A": "Wednesday",
      "B": "Friday",
      "C": "Saturday",
      "D": "Sunday"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Frankie the Frog had an accident and broke one of his legs. He went to the hospital on Monday, November 1 and left on November 30. What day of the week is it?",
      "Answer": "Tuesday",
      "A": "Tuesday",
      "B": "Friday",
      "C": "Thursday",
      "D": "Sunday"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Rico the Rabbit eats 1 carrot on Sunday, 2 carrots on Monday, 4 carrots on Tuesday, and so on. How many carrots does he eat every week?",
      "Answer": "127 carrots",
      "A": "20 carrots",
      "B": "127 carrots",
      "C": "15 per week",
      "D": "19 carrots"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Fill me up with hot or cold. Put anything in me and I will make sure I\u2019ll hold. What am I?",
      "Answer": "A cup",
      "A": "A sand",
      "B": "A cup",
      "C": "Cloth",
      "D": "Bag"
    },
    {
      "Question": "\u00a0I come down, but I never go up. What am I?",
      "Answer": "Rain",
      "A": "Sun and moon",
      "B": "Lie",
      "C": "Rain",
      "D": "All of the above"
    },
    {
      "Question": "\u00a0I have hands, but I cannot clap. What am I?",
      "Answer": "A clock",
      "A": "Animals",
      "B": "A clock",
      "C": "A baby",
      "D": "None of the above"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0I am full of holes, but I can still hold a lot of water. What am I?",
      "Answer": "A sponge",
      "A": "A sponge",
      "B": "A basket",
      "C": "Bowl",
      "D": "Paper"
    },
    {
      "Question": "\u00a0Where are Chinese gooseberries from?",
      "Answer": "New Zealand",
      "A": "Korea",
      "B": "China",
      "C": "New Zealand",
      "D": "Nigeria"
    },
    {
      "Question": "\u00a0What came first, the chicken or the egg?",
      "Answer":
          "The egg.\u00a0Dinosaurs laid eggs long before there were chickens!",
      "A": "The Chicken. There are the ones that lay the eggs",
      "B": "The egg.\u00a0Dinosaurs laid eggs long before there were chickens!",
      "C": "Incubated eggs come first before the chicken",
      "D": "The Hen"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Before Mount Everest was discovered, what was the highest mountain in the world?",
      "Answer": "Mount Everest.",
      "A": "No mountain at the time",
      "B": "Mount Everest.",
      "C": "K2",
      "D": "Makalu"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0What happened in 1961 and will not happen again until 6009?",
      "Answer": "The year will again be the same upside down",
      "A": "I don't know what happened",
      "B": "The year will never come again",
      "C": "The year will again be the same upside down",
      "D": "Nothing happened"
    },
    {
      "Question": " Can you make the letters in NEW DOOR one word?",
      "Answer": "ONE WORD",
      "A": "NewWord",
      "B": "ONE WORD",
      "C": "DOOR",
      "D": "NEW"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "If the red house is on the right side and if the blue house is on the left side where\u2019s the white house?",
      "Answer": "In Washington DC",
      "A": "New york",
      "B": "Opposite the blue house",
      "C": "In Washington DC",
      "D": "By the river"
    },
    {
      "Question": "\u00a0What has a head and a tail but no body?",
      "Answer": "A coin",
      "A": "A leopard",
      "B": "A coin",
      "C": "River",
      "D": "Wire"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0There was a pink one-story house in a cozy\u00a0neighborhood. Everything in it was pink \u2013 the walls, the carpets, the furniture, even the cat! What color were the stairs?",
      "Answer": "There were no stairs. It\u2019s a one-story house!",
      "A": "It's a two story house with pick colors",
      "B": "There were no stairs. It\u2019s a one-story house",
      "C": "There are pink",
      "D": "No color"
    },
    {
      "Question": " What is Rupert the Bear\u2019s middle name?",
      "Answer": "The",
      "A": "Pert",
      "B": "The",
      "C": "Name",
      "D": "Rupert"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          " If there are three apples & you took away two, how many do you have?",
      "Answer": "Two",
      "A": "Two",
      "B": "Three",
      "C": "5 apples",
      "D": "One apple"
    },
    {
      "Question": "\u00a0What\u2019s the longest word in the English language?",
      "Answer":
          "Smiles. Because there\u2019s a mile between the beginning and the end",
      "A": "Journey",
      "B":
          "Smiles. Because there\u2019s a mile between the beginning and the end",
      "C": "Language",
      "D": "Missisipi"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Ten copycats were sitting in a boat. One jumped out. How many were left?",
      "Answer": "None. They were copycats so they all jumped out!",
      "A": "One. The one that jumped",
      "B": "None. They were copycats so they all jumped out!",
      "C": "Nine copycats were remaining",
      "D": "10"
    },
    {
      "Question": "\u00a0In baseball, how many outs are there in an inning?",
      "Answer": "Six. Each team has 3",
      "A": "Six. Each team has 3",
      "B": "Four. Each team has 2",
      "C": "None",
      "D": "Three"
    },
    {
      "Question": "\u00a0How far can a puppy run into the woods?",
      "Answer": "Halfway. When they get there, they\u2019re on their way out!",
      "A": "Halfway. When they get there, they\u2019re on their way out!",
      "B": "As long as it can run",
      "C": "5 miles",
      "D": "Forever"
    },
    {
      "Question": "\u00a0What gets wetter & wetter the more it dries?",
      "Answer": "A towel",
      "A": "A towel",
      "B": "Ocean",
      "C": "Sponge",
      "D": "Soup"
    },
    {
      "Question": "\u00a0What the exact middle of America?",
      "Answer": "The letter \u201cr\u201d",
      "A": "The letter \u201cr\u201d",
      "B": "Citizen",
      "C": "New York",
      "D": "None"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0What word when written in capital letters is the same backward, frontward and upside down?",
      "Answer": "NOON",
      "A": "EZE",
      "B": "WON",
      "C": "ON",
      "D": "NOON"
    },
    {
      "Question": "\u00a0What two words, when combined hold the most letters?",
      "Answer": "Post Office",
      "A": "Post Office",
      "B": "News Paper",
      "C": "Letter",
      "D": "None of the above"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0A cowboy rode to an inn on Wednesday. He stayed two nights and left on Wednesday. How could that be?",
      "Answer": "His horse was named Wednesday",
      "A": "It's not possible",
      "B": "His horse was named Wednesday",
      "C": "He skipped some days",
      "D": "He never went to the inn"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0What has a mouth but doesn\u2019t eat? A bank with no money? A bed but doesn\u2019t sleep and waves but no hands?",
      "Answer": "A river",
      "A": "Unborn baby",
      "B": "River",
      "C": "A bank",
      "D": "Mosquito"
    },
    {
      "Question": " Jeff\u2019s dad has three sons: Snap, Crackle, and ___?",
      "Answer": "Jeff",
      "A": "Sophia",
      "B": "Destiny",
      "C": "Jeff",
      "D": "Jesy"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0A man went outside in the pouring rain with no protection, but not a single hair on his head got wet. How come?",
      "Answer": "The man was bald",
      "A": "The man has no head",
      "B": "The man was bald",
      "C": "He was wearing a hat",
      "D": "He went out with umbrella"
    },
    {
      "Question": " What never gets any wetter, no matter how much it rains?",
      "Answer": "The ocean",
      "A": "Coat",
      "B": "The ocean",
      "C": "Umbrella",
      "D": "Rubber"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0You\u2019re a bus driver. At the first stop, 4 people get on. At the second stop, 8 people get on, at the third stop 2 people get off and, at the forth stop everyone got off. The question is what color are the bus driver\u2019s eyes?",
      "Answer": "Whatever color eyes you have!",
      "A": "Grey eyes",
      "B": "Blue eyes",
      "C": "Whatever color others have!",
      "D": "Whatever color eyes you have!"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0If there\u2019s a frog, dead in the center of a lily pad which is right in the middle of the pond, which side would it jump to?",
      "Answer": "Neither, the frog is dead",
      "A": "It will sink",
      "B": "To the left side of the pond",
      "C": "Either left or right",
      "D": "Neither, the frog is dead"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Twelve pears hanging high, twelve men passing by, each took a pear and left eleven hanging there. How can eleven pears be left?",
      "Answer": "\u201cEach\u201d was a man\u2019s name",
      "A": "Each men came with their own pear",
      "B": "They replaced the pears after collecting it",
      "C": "\u201cEach\u201d was a man\u2019s name",
      "D": "I don't know"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0If a plane crashed on the border of England and Scotland, where would they bury the survivors?",
      "Answer": "You don\u2019t bury survivors",
      "A": "At the cemetary",
      "B": "Between England and Scotland",
      "C": "Their body will be disposed",
      "D": "You don\u2019t bury survivors"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Agatha\u2019s mother has five different daughters. One\u2019s name is Danielle, one\u2019s name is Brittany, one\u2019s name is Samantha, another is named Rebecca. What\u2019s the name of the fifth daughter?",
      "Answer": "Agatha",
      "A": "Happiness",
      "B": "Sophia",
      "C": "Agatha",
      "D": "Diamond"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Do you know the name of the invention that lets you look instantly right through any wall you want?",
      "Answer": "A window",
      "A": "Transparent Wall",
      "B": "A window",
      "C": "A mirror",
      "D": "None"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Can you think of something that\u2019s as light as a feather but even the world\u2019s strongest human couldn\u2019t hold it for any longer than a minute?",
      "Answer": "Your breath",
      "A": "Water",
      "B": "Bird Feather",
      "C": "Your breath",
      "D": "Air"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0\u00a0I am filled with keys but have no locks. I have space but there are no extra rooms. Sure, you can enter but there is absolutely no exit. What am I?",
      "Answer": "A keyboard",
      "A": "The future",
      "B": "A keyboard",
      "C": "A cave",
      "D": "MasterClass"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0\u00a0If you see an electric train headed east at 70 an hour but there is a wind blowing in from the west at 80 miles an hour, which way is the smoke from the train going to blow?",
      "Answer": "An electric train doesn\u2019t have smoke",
      "A": "It will blow on all directions",
      "B": "To the east",
      "C": "Either north or south",
      "D": "An electric train doesn\u2019t have smoke"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Can you think of something that goes all around the woods but never actually goes into the wood at all?",
      "Answer": "Tree bark",
      "A": "Wire cracker",
      "B": "Smoke",
      "C": "Tree bark",
      "D": "None"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Do you know what goes up and down every minute of every day but never actually moves?",
      "Answer": "The temperature",
      "A": "Your heart",
      "B": "The sun",
      "C": "The temperature",
      "D": "Wind"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          " What is something you can serve but shouldn\u2019t ever eat?",
      "Answer": "A volleyball",
      "A": "A volleyball",
      "B": "Shawarma",
      "C": "Your servant",
      "D": "All of the above"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0What is something people bite to eat but then never actually eat in the first place?",
      "Answer": "Silverware and plates",
      "A": "Rollone",
      "B": "Silverware and plates",
      "C": "Food",
      "D": "Meat"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0\u00a0Do you know where you can find cities and countries, towns and shops, roads and lakes, but absolutely no people whatsoever?",
      "Answer": "A map",
      "A": "Country side",
      "B": "A map",
      "C": "The continent",
      "D": "Every where"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0If everything goes wrong, completely sideways, what is something you can always count on?",
      "Answer": "Your fingers and toes",
      "A": "Every one around you",
      "B": "Your fingers and toes",
      "C": "Love",
      "D": "Your conciousness"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0There\u2019s a question that you can never answer yes to. Do you know what it is?",
      "Answer": "Are you asleep yet?",
      "A": "Who Murdered them",
      "B": "Did you kill the man",
      "C": "Are you asleep yet?",
      "D": "When will you wake"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Can you think of something that travels all over the planet but always stays in the exact same spot?",
      "Answer": "A stamp",
      "A": "Earth",
      "B": "A stamp",
      "C": "The moon",
      "D": "Sun"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Draw a line on a piece of paper. Without touching that line, how can you\u00a0make it longer?",
      "Answer": "Draw a short line right next to it.",
      "A": "I dont't know",
      "B": "Draw a short line right next to it.",
      "C": "Not possible, You must touch the line",
      "D": "Draw the line with a metre rule"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0I am an odd number, but if you take away just a single letter I become even. Can you guess my number?",
      "Answer": "Seven",
      "A": "Seven",
      "B": "Nine",
      "C": "Eleven",
      "D": "Fifteen"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0A city bus sets out for the morning with no passengers on board. At the first stop, two people get on, at the next stop five more. One after that, seven people get on and three people get off. At the following stop, five people get on and six people get off. The last stop has three people getting on and one people getting off. How many stops were made?",
      "Answer": "Five stops",
      "A": "Three stops",
      "B": "Four stops",
      "C": "Five stops",
      "D": "Just 10 stops"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Put together Tom and his father and they weigh\u00a0280 pounds. Tom\u2019s dad weighs three times as much as he does. How much does Tom weigh?",
      "Answer": "70 pounds",
      "A": "Same as his dad",
      "B": "30 pounds in total",
      "C": "140 pounds",
      "D": "70 pounds"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0What two numbers make a one-digit number when you multiply them but a two-digit number when you add them together?",
      "Answer": "One and nine",
      "A": "One and One",
      "B": "One and nine",
      "C": "Five and Five",
      "D": "Two and Nine"
    },
    {
      "Question": "\u00a0How many double-digit numbers are there?",
      "Answer": "92",
      "A": "103",
      "B": "92",
      "C": "26",
      "D": "6"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Billy tells his sister Sarah that he is twice as old and twice as smart as her right now. Sarah says that in five years should be twice as old as she is now and that Billy won\u2019t be. How old will they be in five years?\u00a0",
      "Answer": "Billy will be 15 and Sarah will be 10",
      "A": "Sarah will be twice as old as Billy",
      "B": "Billy will be 15 and Sarah will be 10",
      "C": "Sarah will be 15 and Billy will be 10",
      "D": "Billy will be younger than Sarah"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0If you were born in an odd-numbered\u00a0year will you celebrate your 50th birthday in an odd or even year?",
      "Answer": "Odd",
      "A": "Odd",
      "B": "Either Odd or Even",
      "C": "Even",
      "D": "Neither"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Mother\u2019s Day is always the second Sunday in the month of May. When is the earliest day it could be?\u00a0",
      "Answer": "May 8th",
      "A": "After Good friday",
      "B": "May 8th",
      "C": "During Esther day",
      "D": "May 5th"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Four friends are racing. Lisa finishes four hours ahead of Tony, with Pete finishing eight hours ahead of Max. Max needed six more hours to finish than Lisa. What order do they cross the finish line in?",
      "Answer": "Pete, Lisa, Tony, Max",
      "A": "Pete, Tony, Max, Lisa",
      "B": "Pete, Lisa, Tony, Max",
      "C": "Lisa, Tony, Max",
      "D": "Tony, Max, Pete, Lisa"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0If only these letters were written down \u2013 J FM AM J JAS OND \u2013 what would they mean?",
      "Answer": "The first letter of every month in a year",
      "A": "The first letter of every month in a year",
      "B": "I don't know",
      "C": "The first word in every day of the month",
      "D": "The second and last letter in every month in a year"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          " 16 players enter into a basketball shootout tournament. How many games have to happen before a winner is announced?",
      "Answer": "15",
      "A": "7",
      "B": "15",
      "C": "2",
      "D": "Until a winner is announced"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          " If you rolled a single die just once, would you be least likely to roll an odd number, number larger than three, or a number smaller than three?",
      "Answer": "A number smaller than three",
      "A": "A number smaller than three",
      "B": "A number smaller than three",
      "C": "Number larger than three",
      "D": "All 6 numbers"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0What object doesn\u2019t belong in this list \u2013 trumpet, flute, violin, harmonica, tuba?",
      "Answer": "Violin",
      "A": "Harmonica",
      "B": "Violin",
      "C": "tuba",
      "D": "Flute"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Mrs. Adams tells her neighbor that her son turns 16 today and that next birthday he\u2019ll be 20. How can that be?",
      "Answer": "He was born on February 29, a leap year",
      "A": "I don't know",
      "B": "He was born on February 29, a leap year",
      "C": "On his next 4th year",
      "D": "It's never possible"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0What does this secret message say? Tha twasn treall ys oh ardaf terall",
      "Answer": "That wasn\u2019t really so hard after all",
      "A": "That wasn\u2019t really so hard after all",
      "B": "Tha twasn treall ys oh ardaf terall",
      "C": "I don't know",
      "D": "it said nothing"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0A baker carries a bag of flour that weighs 15 pounds. He takes half of the flour out, but finds the bag weighs 9 pounds. How heavy is the empty bag?",
      "Answer": "3 pounds",
      "A": "4 pounds",
      "B": "15 pounds",
      "C": "3 pounds",
      "D": "10 pounds"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Amy is 14 and her mother is 38. How many years ago was her mother exactly 3 times as old as Amy?",
      "Answer": "2 years ago",
      "A": "4 years ago",
      "B": "5 years ago",
      "C": "2 years ago",
      "D": "Just 5 years"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0If days on Mars are as long as two weeks on Earth, how long is an hour?",
      "Answer": "14 Earth hours",
      "A": "12 Earth hours",
      "B": "14 Earth hours",
      "C": "2 hours",
      "D": "I dont't know"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Cara leaves New York at eight in the morning, driving 35 mph. Nancy starts driving to New York at a speed of 50 mph. When they meet a which one will be furthest away from New York?",
      "Answer":
          "When they meet, they will be the same distance away from New York",
      "A": "They will never meet",
      "B": "When they meet, they will be the same distance away from New York",
      "C": "Cara will be further away from New York",
      "D": "Nancy will be futherst away from New York"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0A teacher says that there are fewer than 30 students but more than 20 in a classroom. The children can be divided into groups of two, three, four, six, and eight with no leftovers. How many students are there?",
      "Answer": "24 students",
      "A": "Only 14 students",
      "B": "24 students",
      "C": "12 students",
      "D": "36 students"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0\u00a0If you counted up all of the ears in the country and then divided that number by two, what would you know for sure?",
      "Answer": "How many living creatures lived in the country.",
      "A": "Next question please ",
      "B": "How many living creatures lived in the country.",
      "C": "Total number of creatures in the state",
      "D": "Every creature has two ears"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Max and Ross\u00a0find of lettuce with 20 individual leaves. Because Max found the lettuce first he gets an extra leaf than his friend. How many leaves does Max get?",
      "Answer": "10 1/2 leaves",
      "A": "15 leaves",
      "B": "11 leaves",
      "C": "10 1/2 leaves",
      "D": "3 leaves"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Which two numbers come out the same whether you multiply or add them together?",
      "Answer": "2\u00d72=4 2+2=4",
      "A": "2\u00d72=4 2+2=4",
      "B": "1x1=1 1+1=2",
      "C": "3x3=6 3+3=6",
      "D": "All of the above"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0If every month had exactly 30 days instead of some with 29, some with 30, and some with 31 would each year be longer or shorter?",
      "Answer": "Shorter (360 days).",
      "A": "Shorter (360 days).",
      "B": "Longer",
      "C": "In between",
      "D": "Longer (366 days)"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0\u00a0Mr. Walsh is exactly 5 times as old as his dog Patches. In five years, Mr. Walsh will only be three times as old as Patches. How old will he be in five years?",
      "Answer": "30",
      "A": "20",
      "B": "30",
      "C": "35",
      "D": "25"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Seven brothers were born two years apart. The youngest brother is seven. How old is the oldest brother?",
      "Answer": "19",
      "A": "19",
      "B": "34",
      "C": "21",
      "D": "16"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Every year on Mars is double the length of a year on earth, how old would you be if you lived on Mars?",
      "Answer": "Double your age",
      "A": "200 years",
      "B": "Double your age",
      "C": "Your age won't change",
      "D": "1/2 your age"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0What\u2019s the biggest number you can make with the numbers three, five, and seven?",
      "Answer": "753",
      "A": "15",
      "B": "357",
      "C": "573",
      "D": "753"
    },
    {
      "Question": "\u00a0What uneven numbers are between 10 and 16?",
      "Answer": "11,13,15",
      "A": "10 to 14",
      "B": "11,13,15",
      "C": "12,13,15",
      "D": "13,15,12"
    },
    {
      "Question": "\u00a0Which multiples of four are found between 10 and 19?",
      "Answer": "12 and 16",
      "A": "10 and 12",
      "B": "12 and 16",
      "C": "12 and 18",
      "D": "All of the above"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0A new movie comes out with the first people showing up an hour before showtime. The audience doubles every 10 minutes, and after 60 minutes the theater is full. When was the theater half full?",
      "Answer": "10 minutes before show time",
      "A": "10 minutes before show time",
      "B": "An hour later",
      "C": "Morning and night",
      "D": "10 minutes after show time"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Maggie lives on a street with 10 houses. The houses are numbered 1 to 10. If Maggie adds up all the house numbers that are lower than hers, the total is three times her actual house number. What number is Maggie\u2019s house?",
      "Answer": "House number 7",
      "A": "9",
      "B": "House number 7",
      "C": "8",
      "D": "Number 10"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Was the smallest amount of coins you can use to get exactly \$0.65",
      "Answer": "Two quarters, dime, and a nickel.",
      "A": "1 Naira",
      "B": "Zero coin",
      "C": "Two quarters, dime, and a nickel.",
      "D": "Three grands"
    },
    {
      "Question": " What are three things that are only sold in pairs?\u00a0",
      "Answer": "Gloves, shoes, socks",
      "A": "Pot, Cooker and Knife",
      "B": "Gloves, shoes, socks",
      "C": "Bag to school",
      "D": "Pencils"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Lisa is William\u2019s niece, but she isn\u2019t Emily\u2019s niece \u2013 even though Emily is William\u2019s sister and William isn\u2019t married. How is that possible?",
      "Answer": "Lisa is Emily\u2019s daughter",
      "A": "Don't know",
      "B": "They are all cousins",
      "C": "Then Willian is not Lisa's Nephew",
      "D": "Lisa is Emily\u2019s daughter"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0\u00a0A cookie jar has 10 chocolate chip cookies and 10 peanut butter cookies. How many cookies would you have to take out to get two of each kind?",
      "Answer": "12 cookies",
      "A": "Don't know",
      "B": "3 cookies",
      "C": "12 cookies",
      "D": "No cookies"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Laura says that she can throw a ball so that it flies away from her, will change direction suddenly, and then come right back to her all by itself. Is that even possible?",
      "Answer": "Yes, if she throws it straight in the air!",
      "A": "Yes, but don't know how",
      "B": "it's not possible",
      "C": "Yes, if she throws it straight in the air!",
      "D": "Some how"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Liz orders six bowls of ice cream with three scoops in each. Ben wants as many scoops as her, but in just two dishes. How many scoops are in each of his dishes?",
      "Answer": "Nine in each",
      "A": "Just 8",
      "B": "30 in each",
      "C": "Six in each",
      "D": "Nine in each"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0If five alligators can eat five fish in three minutes, how long will 18 alligators need to eat 18 fish?",
      "Answer": "3 minutes",
      "A": "Not possible",
      "B": "5 minutes",
      "C": "3 minutes",
      "D": "2 minutes"
    },
    {
      "Question": "\u00a0How long did the Hundred Years War last?",
      "Answer": "116 years",
      "A": "Don't know",
      "B": "116 years",
      "C": "400 years",
      "D": "4 years"
    },
    {
      "Question": "\u00a0Which country makes Panama hats?",
      "Answer": "Ecuador",
      "A": "Germany",
      "B": "Nigeria",
      "C": "Uniter states of america",
      "D": "Ecuador"
    },
    {
      "Question": "\u00a0What color is the black box on a commercial airplane?",
      "Answer": "Orange",
      "A": "White",
      "B": "Purple",
      "C": "Orange",
      "D": "Black"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          " In which month do Russians celebrate the October Revolution?",
      "Answer": "November",
      "A": "February",
      "B": "November",
      "C": "October",
      "D": "July"
    },
    {
      "Question": "\u00a0What is a camel\u2019s hair brush made of?",
      "Answer": "Squirrel fur",
      "A": "Shell",
      "B": "Rubber",
      "C": "Fibre",
      "D": "Squirrel fur"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0The Canary Islands in the Pacific are named after what animal?",
      "Answer": "Dogs",
      "A": "Eagle",
      "B": "Dogs",
      "C": "Warthog",
      "D": "Lion"
    },
    {
      "Question": "\u00a0What was King George VI\u2019s first name?",
      "Answer": "Albert",
      "A": "Destiny Ed",
      "B": "Herbert",
      "C": "Albert",
      "D": "George"
    },
    {
      "Question": "\u00a0\u00a0What color is a purple finch?",
      "Answer": "Crimson",
      "A": "Amber",
      "B": "Purple",
      "C": "Crimson",
      "D": "Accent"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0\u00a0I am a ball that can be rolled but never bounced or thrown. What am I?",
      "Answer": "An eyeball",
      "A": "An eyeball",
      "B": "Volley ball",
      "C": "Football",
      "D": "All of the above"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0You can catch me, but you can\u2019t throw me. What am I?",
      "Answer": "A cold",
      "A": "Stone",
      "B": "A cold",
      "C": "Apple",
      "D": "Train"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0The more you take away from me, the larger I become. What am I?",
      "Answer": "A hole",
      "A": "A hole",
      "B": "Water",
      "C": "A sand",
      "D": "Money"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0The Jones family started driving south for their summer vacation, going through five different states along the way. The Bradfords are driving in the opposite direction and only went through three states. What direction are they driving in?",
      "Answer": "North",
      "A": "East",
      "B": "North",
      "C": "South",
      "D": "West"
    },
    {
      "Question":
          "\u00a0Mr. and Mrs. Fredrickson are eating ice cream. Mrs. Fredrickson says that if her husband gives her one scoop of his ice cream she\u2019ll have twice as many scoops as him. Mr. Fredrickson says that if she gives him one of her scoops available have the same amount. How many scoops do they each have?",
      "Answer":
          "Mrs. Fredrickson has seven scoops and Mr. Fredrickson has five.",
      "A": "Mr. Fredrickson has seven scoops and Mrs. Fredrickson has five.",
      "B": "Mrs. Fredrickson has seven scoops and Mr. Fredrickson has five.",
      "C": "I don't know",
      "D": "Mrs. Fredrickson has eight scoops and Mr. Fredrickson has nine."
    }
  ]..shuffle();
}
